1
00:00:16,385 --> 00:00:17,777
为毛我们同意跑到乡下
Why did we agree to do Thanksgiving

2
00:00:17,787 --> 00:00:19,813
和布鲁克的家人过感恩节啊
in the suburbs with Brooke's family?

3
00:00:19,823 --> 00:00:21,581
人家的乡村恐惧症要犯了
My S.P.D. Is flaring up.

4
00:00:21,591 --> 00:00:23,283
亲爱的 乡村恐惧症
Honey, Suburban Panic Disorder

5
00:00:23,293 --> 00:00:24,717
就没这种说法好吗
is not a real thing.

6
00:00:24,727 --> 00:00:27,220
那为什么我腋下生汗 口干舌燥的
Tell that to my pit stains and cottonmouth.

7
00:00:27,230 --> 00:00:28,855
其实我对乡下也一般
I don't care for the suburbs either, hon but

8
00:00:28,865 --> 00:00:30,824
但至少风景迷人 不是吗
at least they're beautiful.

9
00:00:30,834 --> 00:00:31,925
是吗
Are they?

10
00:00:31,935 --> 00:00:33,159
玉盘珍馐
Behind all the potlucks

11
00:00:33,169 --> 00:00:35,128
衣着光鲜背后
and Lilly Pulitzer shift dresses

12
00:00:35,138 --> 00:00:37,630
他们都藏着腹黑的心
lurks an insidious darkness.

13
00:00:37,640 --> 00:00:39,332
男的都会喝得酩酊大醉
All the husbands are alkies.

14
00:00:39,342 --> 00:00:42,335
女的就猛嗑药
All the wives are popping pills like Tic Tacs.

15
00:00:42,345 --> 00:00:45,338
地窖下面还藏着 穿皮革拘束衣的猛男
I'm talking Zipper Mouthed Leather Man in the cellar.

16
00:00:45,348 --> 00:00:47,974
好吧 我收回刚刚的话
Okay, I take that back, you 100% have

17
00:00:47,984 --> 00:00:49,275
你绝对有乡村恐惧症
Suburban Panic Disorder.

18
00:00:49,285 --> 00:00:50,410
我们可是要和真正的清教徒
We're about to have Thanksgiving

19
00:00:50,420 --> 00:00:52,312
一起过感恩节了呀
with actual Puritans.

20
00:00:52,322 --> 00:00:54,047
他们有的人近亲结婚
Some of them are so inbred,

21
00:00:54,057 --> 00:00:55,381
一出生就有六根手指
that they're born with a sixth finger

22
00:00:55,391 --> 00:00:57,217
然后截掉多余那根
that they have removed at birth.

23
00:00:57,227 --> 00:01:00,253
娃们 第一个找到手上有截肢痕迹的 赏五块
Hey! Five bucks to the first person who feels a nub!

24
00:01:00,263 --> 00:01:02,322
- 好棒 - 耶
- Yeah! - Yes!

25
00:01:02,332 --> 00:01:03,890
娃们 你妈净瞎扯
Kids, none of this is true.

26
00:01:06,135 --> 00:01:08,828
谁说得 我们得想一个家庭安全词
Really? We need a family safe word.

27
00:01:08,838 --> 00:01:10,430
如果有人需要救援
If anyone is in need of a rescue,

28
00:01:10,440 --> 00:01:12,832
就说 袋子底 听见了吗
just say "Cul de Sac" Okay?

29
00:01:12,842 --> 00:01:14,701
听听就好了 孩子们
Nod and smile, kids.

30
00:01:14,711 --> 00:01:16,202
今天 我要揭穿这个
Today I'm going to blow the lid off

31
00:01:16,212 --> 00:01:19,714
乡村皆秀美的谎言
the lie that is the "Perfect" Suburbs.

32
00:01:22,946 --> 00:01:27,370
怪妈闯荡上东区

33
00:01:27,857 --> 00:01:30,683
巴洛特 你家真有过节的气氛啊
Barrett, your home is so festive.

34
00:01:30,693 --> 00:01:32,819
如果你的祖先是第一批移民
Aw, well when one's ancestors

35
00:01:32,829 --> 00:01:34,220
乘着五月花号来到美国的
came over on the Mayflower

36
00:01:34,230 --> 00:01:36,990
感恩节的时候就会大肆庆祝(overboard)
one tends to go overboard on Thanksgiving.

37
00:01:37,000 --> 00:01:38,725
不是开双关语玩笑（overboard有跌落水中的意思）
No pun intended.

38
00:01:38,735 --> 00:01:40,226
听到了吗 安迪
You hear that, Andy?

39
00:01:40,236 --> 00:01:42,262
巴洛特的祖先是清教徒的祖先呢
Barrett's ancestors were Pilgrims.

40
00:01:42,272 --> 00:01:43,396
我还真不知道 
I had no idea.

41
00:01:43,406 --> 00:01:45,031
我们无处不在
We're everywhere.

42
00:01:45,041 --> 00:01:46,933
这整个镇都有点血缘关系呢
The whole town is probably related.

43
00:01:46,943 --> 00:01:48,301
嗨 你们到了
Hi gang!

44
00:01:48,311 --> 00:01:50,136
撒切尔 不然你带小盆友们
Thatcher, why don't you take the children

45
00:01:50,146 --> 00:01:52,213
去楼上彩排吧
upstairs to rehearse?

46
00:01:54,083 --> 00:01:55,708
撒切尔写了一个
Thatcher wrote a play

47
00:01:55,718 --> 00:01:58,411
和最早感恩节有关的话剧
about the very first Thanksgiving.

48
00:01:58,421 --> 00:01:59,879
我们会成为最好的朋友的
We're going to be best friends!

49
00:01:59,889 --> 00:02:01,314
好有爱
Aw!

50
00:02:01,324 --> 00:02:03,049
我要让你做我的小婊砸
I'm gonna make you my bitch.

51
00:02:03,059 --> 00:02:04,717
袋子
Cul de...!

52
00:02:04,727 --> 00:02:06,886
- 感恩节快乐 - 你也是 伯克利
- Happy Thanksgiving! - You too, Berkley.

53
00:02:06,896 --> 00:02:08,221
还记得我丈夫吗 洛克哈特
You remember my husband, Lockhart?

54
00:02:08,231 --> 00:02:09,822
当然了 很高兴见到你
Absolutely, nice to see you.

55
00:02:09,832 --> 00:02:11,999
洛克哈特啊 真是荣幸呢
Lockhart, a pleasure.

56
00:02:12,969 --> 00:02:15,094
- 没有第六指 - 客气点
- No nub. - Play nice.

57
00:02:15,104 --> 00:02:17,294
给那边的霍索恩打个招呼吧
Oh and give a wave to Hawthorn over there.

58
00:02:18,684 --> 00:02:19,894
所以啊 安迪
So, Andy. How long did it

59
00:02:19,895 --> 00:02:22,268
从市里开过来要多久啊 半个小时吗
take you to get here from the city? Half an hour?

60
00:02:22,278 --> 00:02:23,970
你知道吗 住在这里人都说是半个小时
You know, everyone who lives out here says

61
00:02:23,980 --> 00:02:26,372
但也得一个小时
it's a half an hour, but it's always an hour.

62
00:02:26,382 --> 00:02:27,407
看样子来了个小心翼翼遵守交规
Sounds like we got a city slicker

63
00:02:27,417 --> 00:02:31,377
不敢开到应急车道的城里男人啊
who's too chicken to drive on the shoulder!

64
00:02:31,387 --> 00:02:32,979
确实我来这花的时间要多一些
It may have taken me a little longer to get out here,

65
00:02:32,989 --> 00:02:34,447
但我可是全速三十三英里
but I did make it the full 33 miles

66
00:02:34,457 --> 00:02:36,316
- 电动行驶哦 - 不会吧
- on electricity only. - No?

67
00:02:36,326 --> 00:02:38,384
- 是啊 - 你走的是九十五大道还是
- Yeah. - You take 95

68
00:02:38,394 --> 00:02:39,452
- 梅里特大道 - 梅里特啊
- or the Merritt? - The Merritt.

69
00:02:39,462 --> 00:02:40,753
- 是吗 - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.

70
00:02:40,763 --> 00:02:42,703
天呐 他们在讨论路线 杀了我吧
God, they're talking routes, shoot me!

71
00:02:42,713 --> 00:02:43,967
应该走梅里特的
The Merrit's the way to go.

72
00:02:43,977 --> 00:02:45,825
- 对 走梅里特大道 -绝对的
- Yeah the Merritt. - Definitely.

73
00:02:45,835 --> 00:02:48,161
这个 四号宝贝啊
Oh well. Baby number four!

74
00:02:48,171 --> 00:02:49,535
其实是第五个了
It's five actually.

75
00:02:49,847 --> 00:02:52,098
第五个 梅兹尔
Five?! Mazel.

76
00:02:52,108 --> 00:02:54,167
- 知道是男孩还是女孩吗 - 明天就知道了
- Do you know what you're having? - We'll find out tomorrow.

77
00:02:54,177 --> 00:02:57,236
我们要举办一个伯克利的性别揭晓派对
I am actually hosting Berkley's gender reveal party.

78
00:02:57,246 --> 00:02:58,338
真棒
Yeah!

79
00:02:58,348 --> 00:02:59,472
就像你打开一个盒子
Oh, like where you open a box

80
00:02:59,482 --> 00:03:01,240
如果是粉色气球飞出来 就是女孩
and if pink balloons shoot out, it's a girl,

81
00:03:01,250 --> 00:03:03,109
如果是蓝色气球 就是男孩吗
and if they're blue, it's a boy?

82
00:03:03,119 --> 00:03:05,878
吉尔 气球一年能造成数十只鸟的死亡
Balloons murder tens of birds a year, Jill.

83
00:03:05,888 --> 00:03:07,847
但和你说的差不多
So I guess it's the same thing,

84
00:03:07,857 --> 00:03:09,816
除了大规模杀伤鸟
minus the mass casualties.

85
00:03:09,826 --> 00:03:10,850
你也该来的
You should come!

86
00:03:10,860 --> 00:03:12,251
巴洛特的派对可是镇上的话题之王
Barrett's parties are the talk of the township.

87
00:03:12,261 --> 00:03:13,820
她是最好的姐姐了
She's the best sister ever.

88
00:03:13,830 --> 00:03:15,121
最好的举办者吧
Best hostess ever.

89
00:03:15,131 --> 00:03:16,889
真不敢相信你们既庆祝感恩节
I can't believe you're hosting Thanksgiving

90
00:03:16,899 --> 00:03:18,992
又在黑色星期五办派对
and then another party on "Black Friday."

91
00:03:19,002 --> 00:03:22,195
吉尔 我们今天不聊政治 好吗
Oh Jill, let's not discuss politics today, okay?

92
00:03:22,205 --> 00:03:23,997
我是说 双十一啊
No, I meant the shopping stampede.

93
00:03:24,007 --> 00:03:25,365
还是别说了
Let's not.

94
00:03:25,375 --> 00:03:27,934
好吧 那我就转转去吧
Okay. I'm just gonna get...

95
00:03:27,944 --> 00:03:30,069
谢谢您了
Thanks.

96
00:03:30,079 --> 00:03:32,805
我快死了 布鲁克和莱克斯呢
Dying. Where are Brooke and Lex?

97
00:03:32,815 --> 00:03:33,906
莱克斯十分钟前发短信给我
Lex texted me ten minutes ago.

98
00:03:33,916 --> 00:03:35,041
他们才打到优步
They just got in the Uber.

99
00:03:35,051 --> 00:03:36,442
十分钟前
Ten minutes ago?

100
00:03:36,452 --> 00:03:37,877
他们为什么不自己开车呢
Why didn't they take their own car?

101
00:03:37,887 --> 00:03:39,445
我不知道啊
I don't know.

102
00:03:39,789 --> 00:03:40,913
深呼吸
Deep breaths.

103
00:03:40,923 --> 00:03:42,248
我撑不住了
I'm not gonna make it.

104
00:03:42,258 --> 00:03:44,817
我就不是在乡下待的料 看看我
I don't belong in the suburbs. Look at me!

105
00:03:44,827 --> 00:03:47,820
我穿的可是剪刀手爱德华啊 但我又没有剪刀手
I'm Edward Scissorhands but without scissors for hands.

106
00:03:47,830 --> 00:03:49,055
你不是
You are not...

107
00:03:52,168 --> 00:03:54,127
你就是剪刀手爱德华啊
You are like Edward Scissorhands.

108
00:03:56,839 --> 00:03:58,898
大家感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving, everyone!

109
00:03:58,908 --> 00:04:00,533
不好意思 我们是最后一波来的
Sorry, we're the last ones!

110
00:04:00,543 --> 00:04:03,369
我们的优步飞机晚了
Our Uber chopper was late!

111
00:04:03,379 --> 00:04:04,871
也不是你们的错
What can you do?

112
00:04:04,881 --> 00:04:06,839
能搭把手吗
Can I get the help?

113
00:04:06,849 --> 00:04:08,215
谢谢
Thank you.

114
00:04:11,187 --> 00:04:12,320
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.

115
00:04:12,330 --> 00:04:14,247
你也是 你怎么了
You too. What happened?

116
00:04:14,257 --> 00:04:17,216
跳体操的旧伤
Oh, uh. Old vaulting injury.

117
00:04:17,226 --> 00:04:19,052
十年前的奥运会上扭伤了脚踝
I sprained my ankle in the Olympics ten years ago.

118
00:04:19,062 --> 00:04:20,420
真的吗
Really?

119
00:04:20,430 --> 00:04:23,322
不 那是克里 斯扎格（体操运动员）
Nah, that was Kerry Strug.

120
00:04:23,332 --> 00:04:24,457
我只是不好意思告诉你
I'm just too embarrassed to tell you

121
00:04:24,467 --> 00:04:27,293
我是吃甜甜圈的时候从马路牙子上滑倒
I slipped off a curb while eating a donut

122
00:04:27,303 --> 00:04:28,895
就成现在这样了
and now this happens sometimes.

123
00:04:28,905 --> 00:04:30,163
肿吗
Is it swollen?

124
00:04:30,173 --> 00:04:32,465
我觉得医学术语该是 脚踝裸肉
I believe the proper medical term is "Cankle?"

125
00:04:32,475 --> 00:04:34,467
其实是 外周性水肿
Actually, it's "Peripheral edema."

126
00:04:34,477 --> 00:04:36,836
- 你需要米(RICE) - 像烤肉拌饭吗
- You need RICE. - Like pilaf?

127
00:04:36,846 --> 00:04:40,873
休息 冰敷 按压 抬高
Rest, Ice, Compression, Elevation?

128
00:04:40,883 --> 00:04:42,375
你怎么知道的
Wow, how do you know that?

129
00:04:42,385 --> 00:04:44,844
嗯 其实我不怎么和
Um, I don't usually tell people

130
00:04:44,854 --> 00:04:46,846
邻居们讲这个事的
in the building this but...

131
00:04:46,856 --> 00:04:47,914
我是急诊医生
I'm an ER doctor.

132
00:04:47,924 --> 00:04:49,882
太棒了啊
That's awesome.

133
00:04:49,892 --> 00:04:51,250
为什么不想告诉别人啊
Why don't you want people to know?

134
00:04:51,260 --> 00:04:54,220
在医学院 有这么个说法
In med school, you hear these urban legends.

135
00:04:54,230 --> 00:04:55,421
如果你是医生的消息传出去了
If word gets out you're a doctor,

136
00:04:55,431 --> 00:04:57,290
左邻右舍会不分昼夜地跑你家来
neighbors will stop by day and night

137
00:04:57,300 --> 00:05:00,093
叫你看看他们的痣啊
asking you to check out their weird mole

138
00:05:00,103 --> 00:05:02,161
或者开个药 芬太尼（止痛药）
or prescribe Fentanyl.

139
00:05:02,171 --> 00:05:03,463
你是说你没有芬太尼
Are you saying you don't have any Fentanyl?

140
00:05:03,473 --> 00:05:04,997
还是说你不想和别人分享
Or that you won't share it?

141
00:05:05,007 --> 00:05:08,935
我知道听起来很蠢 但我保持低调
I know, it's silly, but I've kept it quiet.

142
00:05:08,945 --> 00:05:10,436
现在只有你知道
Until now.

143
00:05:10,446 --> 00:05:12,205
是我的荣幸
Well, I'm honored.

144
00:05:12,215 --> 00:05:13,906
如果你的脚踝或者
And if you need anything for your ankle

145
00:05:13,916 --> 00:05:18,444
有其他需要求的话 就过来吧
or whatever, um, stop by.

146
00:05:18,454 --> 00:05:20,313
我在2楼
I'm 2F.

147
00:05:20,323 --> 00:05:24,125
2楼啊 好的
2F. Got that.

148
00:05:24,927 --> 00:05:27,353
我觉得这个温特的羊角花篮
I think this cornucopia from Ron Wendt

149
00:05:27,363 --> 00:05:29,455
会给这里起画龙点睛的作用
will add the perfect finishing touch.

150
00:05:29,465 --> 00:05:33,626
他可是纽约市最牛逼的花匠呢
He's the florist in New York City.

151
00:05:33,636 --> 00:05:35,394
我自己做了一个
I actually crafted my own.

152
00:05:35,404 --> 00:05:38,998
看见了
I- I-I see that.

153
00:05:39,008 --> 00:05:41,601
但我们会把你的放在孩子们的桌子上
But we'll put yours on the kiddie table.

154
00:05:41,611 --> 00:05:43,369
太棒了 如果带点更大的
Great! Bringing anything larger

155
00:05:43,379 --> 00:05:45,238
就会显得太拘谨了
would have been gauche.

156
00:05:45,248 --> 00:05:47,140
杰奎琳（总统肯尼迪夫人）说过  
Jackie O said "Gauche" Is a word reserved

157
00:05:47,150 --> 00:05:49,509
资产阶级的人才说  拘谨 这个词
only for the bourgeois.

158
00:05:49,519 --> 00:05:52,653
她还说过 脱了衣服来骑行吧
Well, she also said, "Let's ride with the top down today."

159
00:05:55,124 --> 00:05:57,374
莱克斯 跟我们说说
Lex, so tell us,

160
00:05:57,384 --> 00:06:00,286
被媳妇养着 是种什么感觉
what is it like to be a kept man?

161
00:06:00,296 --> 00:06:02,288
你老婆会把你的蛋蛋放在冯 韦伯包包里吗
Does your wife keep your balls in a Von Weber purse?

162
00:06:02,298 --> 00:06:04,957
还是放在高到你够不着的架子上
Or just up on a high shelf where you can't reach them?

163
00:06:04,967 --> 00:06:06,325
莱克斯工作很努力
Actually, Lex works very hard...

164
00:06:06,335 --> 00:06:07,560
嘿 没事 兄弟
Hey, it's okay, bro.

165
00:06:07,570 --> 00:06:10,429
洛克哈特就是想
Lockhart's just yanking my chain,

166
00:06:10,439 --> 00:06:12,398
- 惹恼我 - 嘿嘿
- whatever that means. - Yank, yank.

167
00:06:12,408 --> 00:06:13,666
布鲁克正大展宏图
With Brooke doing so well

168
00:06:13,676 --> 00:06:17,136
我就能安心地实现人生追求 而不只是工作了
I can pursue my passion, not just a job.

169
00:06:17,146 --> 00:06:18,971
我不只想着挣钱
I want to make more than money,

170
00:06:18,981 --> 00:06:21,040
我还得留下属于我的光辉一笔
I want to make my mark.

171
00:06:21,050 --> 00:06:22,341
那你计划怎么实现
How do you plan on doing that?

172
00:06:22,351 --> 00:06:25,244
我还没想出来 但是
I haven't figured that out yet but

173
00:06:25,254 --> 00:06:28,181
我可是莱克斯呢
as the CEO of L-E-X

174
00:06:28,191 --> 00:06:31,617
时机到了 我自然会知道
when the moment is right, I'll know.

175
00:06:31,627 --> 00:06:32,985
二十年前霍索恩就是这么说的
Well that's what Hawthorn told himself

176
00:06:32,995 --> 00:06:34,453
看他现在是个什么鬼样
20 years ago and now look at him.

177
00:06:48,972 --> 00:06:50,236
- 嘿 - 嗨
- Hey! - Hi!

178
00:06:50,246 --> 00:06:52,338
看看你 俩完好无缺的胖胖脚踝
Look at you! Two functioning cankles!

179
00:06:52,348 --> 00:06:54,140
是啊 还得多谢你的建议
Yeah, thanks for the advice.

180
00:06:54,150 --> 00:06:57,218
不过我不是为了这个来的
But that's not why I came by.

181
00:06:58,421 --> 00:07:00,446
你能给我女朋友也看一眼吗
Could you take a look at my girlfriend?

182
00:07:00,456 --> 00:07:02,181
她认为西医是父权制
She believes western medicine is a tool

183
00:07:02,191 --> 00:07:03,249
的统治工具
of the patriarchy,

184
00:07:03,259 --> 00:07:04,617
但是她胸口有点痛
but is having chest pains

185
00:07:04,627 --> 00:07:07,119
而我们的助产师去了一个素食主义聚会
and our Doula is hosting a vegan potluck.

186
00:07:07,129 --> 00:07:08,354
你不介意吧
Would you mind?

187
00:07:08,364 --> 00:07:09,655
你女朋友
Your girlfriend?

188
00:07:09,665 --> 00:07:11,924
你这个觉得医生都是魔鬼
Your super pregnant girlfriend

189
00:07:11,934 --> 00:07:13,426
的宝贝怀孕女友
who thinks doctors are the devil.

190
00:07:13,436 --> 00:07:16,095
是的
Yeah.

191
00:07:16,105 --> 00:07:17,163
进来坐吧
Have a seat.

192
00:07:17,173 --> 00:07:20,533
我一会就看一下
I'll be with you in just a minute.

193
00:07:20,543 --> 00:07:24,378
慢点宝贝 实在太感谢你了
Easy babe. Thank you so much.

194
00:07:31,354 --> 00:07:34,180
吉尔 来点自制苹果酒怎么样
Ooh, Jill. How about some homemade hard cider?

195
00:07:34,190 --> 00:07:36,415
第一个感恩节上 清教徒酣饮的那种
It's what the Pilgrims drank at the very first Thanksgiving.

196
00:07:36,425 --> 00:07:38,035
好吧 我也带了好酒来的
Okay, there's also that nice wine I brought.

197
00:07:38,045 --> 00:07:39,352
来点 嗯
There you go. Mm.

198
00:07:39,362 --> 00:07:42,154
好吧 我们大概就得喝这个了 行吧
Okay, I guess we're just having this. Okay.

199
00:07:42,164 --> 00:07:46,425
嗯 颠覆人生的美味 是吧
Yeah, right? Life-changing.

200
00:07:46,435 --> 00:07:48,127
巴洛特是个很棒的厨师
Barrett is an incredible chef.

201
00:07:48,137 --> 00:07:49,295
她自学成才
She is self taught,

202
00:07:49,305 --> 00:07:51,097
一切都是从头开始
makes everything from scratch,

203
00:07:51,107 --> 00:07:53,266
包括织这些餐具垫
even wove these place mats.

204
00:07:53,276 --> 00:07:54,634
我等不及要看看你怎么烹饪
I can't wait to see what you've done with

205
00:07:54,644 --> 00:07:57,203
我送来的那个传统火鸡了
the Heritage Turkey that I sent.

206
00:07:57,213 --> 00:08:00,172
我喜欢火鸡 还有往里面塞馅料和土豆
I love me some turkey, and stuffing, potatoes.

207
00:08:00,182 --> 00:08:04,243
让这些肉汁倾盆而下冲刷我吧
Let a gravy tsunami wash over me.

208
00:08:04,253 --> 00:08:07,713
布鲁克 我把那只火鸡捐给赈济处了
Brooke, I donated that turkey to the soup kitchen.

209
00:08:07,723 --> 00:08:10,182
如我所言 我们会有一个传统的
As I told you, we are having a traditional

210
00:08:10,192 --> 00:08:11,617
感恩节晚餐
Thanksgiving meal.

211
00:08:11,627 --> 00:08:15,087
一六二一年 第一个感恩节上是没有火鸡的
There was no turkey on the menu in 1621.

212
00:08:15,097 --> 00:08:16,389
那吃什么
Oh? What was?

213
00:08:16,399 --> 00:08:18,024
鳗鱼之类的食底泥动物
Eel and other bottom feeders.

214
00:08:18,034 --> 00:08:21,327
葫芦和杂谷粥
Gourds and a mixed grain gruel.

215
00:08:21,337 --> 00:08:22,728
我们今天的晚餐可特别了
Nothing like what we eat today.

216
00:08:22,738 --> 00:08:24,764
所以 没有火鸡
So, no turkey?

217
00:08:24,774 --> 00:08:27,300
没有火鸡
No turkey.

218
00:08:27,310 --> 00:08:28,768
没有馅料
No stuffing?

219
00:08:28,778 --> 00:08:31,137
没有馅料
No stuffing.

220
00:08:31,147 --> 00:08:32,928
救命啊
Cul de Sac.

221
00:08:41,042 --> 00:08:42,534
巴洛特 要我帮你吗
Barrett, can I help you with that?

222
00:08:42,544 --> 00:08:43,668
不用了 谢谢你 吉尔
Oh no thanks, Jill.

223
00:08:43,678 --> 00:08:45,604
这是个熟练活
It takes a deft touch.

224
00:08:45,614 --> 00:08:47,772
我得有什么 手摇执照吗
What do you need, a churner's permit?

225
00:08:47,782 --> 00:08:48,782
不用
No.

226
00:08:51,286 --> 00:08:53,845
第一批移民吃餐前甜点吗
Did the Pilgrims have hor d'ouevres?

227
00:09:02,063 --> 00:09:03,088
在找什么 吉尔
Looking for something, Jill?

228
00:09:03,098 --> 00:09:05,023
厕所
Oh, uh, bathroom.

229
00:09:05,033 --> 00:09:06,391
在这边呢
Oh it's this way.

230
00:09:06,401 --> 00:09:09,135
右手边 第十二个房间
Twelfth door on your right.

231
00:09:11,606 --> 00:09:13,064
所以我在第八球道
So I'm on the 8th fairway,

232
00:09:13,074 --> 00:09:14,299
右边就是太平洋
Pacific Ocean's on my right,

233
00:09:14,309 --> 00:09:15,834
当时风是旋转着吹
winds are swirling around six knots.

234
00:09:15,844 --> 00:09:17,702
你们知道圆石滩上的风怎么打旋的吧
You guys know how the wind swirls at Pebble Beach.

235
00:09:17,712 --> 00:09:19,504
我只要试着
I'm just gonna try to...

236
00:09:19,514 --> 00:09:20,905
用前所未有的轻柔力度
Just ever so gently,

237
00:09:20,915 --> 00:09:23,041
打出去
just... draw it in!

238
00:09:23,051 --> 00:09:26,277
切杆再等球落下
Just chip it and then fall.

239
00:09:26,287 --> 00:09:27,739
离球洞就只有五英尺了
And then five feet to the cup.

240
00:09:27,749 --> 00:09:29,347
- 然后我就 - 你和孩子应该
- So I'm doing this... - You and the kids should

241
00:09:29,357 --> 00:09:31,282
抽时间来城里转转
come into the city some time.

242
00:09:31,292 --> 00:09:33,585
谢谢 只是纽约
Oh thanks. It's just New York.

243
00:09:33,595 --> 00:09:35,920
又有污染 又有恐怖分子
The pollution, the terrorism.

244
00:09:35,930 --> 00:09:37,689
我和你保证 你会很安全
I assure you, you are safe.

245
00:09:37,699 --> 00:09:40,425
你和莱克斯在那养孩子真是太有勇气了
You and Lex are so brave to be raising your kids there.

246
00:09:40,435 --> 00:09:42,494
我们不是有勇气 我们是
We're not brave, it's...

247
00:09:42,504 --> 00:09:44,029
我想洛克哈特和我在健康安全方面
I guess Lockhart and I are fuddy-duddys

248
00:09:44,039 --> 00:09:46,031
就是个守旧的老古板
about health and safety.

249
00:09:46,041 --> 00:09:48,066
我们应该像你们一样
We should be more like you and prioritize

250
00:09:48,076 --> 00:09:51,903
为直升机停机坪 五星餐厅 和水疗放弃一切顾虑
things like helipads, five star restaurants, spas.

251
00:09:51,913 --> 00:09:53,438
- 九十九 一百 - 你在干
- 99, 100. - What are you...

252
00:09:53,448 --> 00:09:54,639
对不起
Oh I'm so sorry.

253
00:09:54,649 --> 00:09:56,908
每隔一百分钟我就要做一百个凯格尔运动
I do 100 kegels every 100 minutes.

254
00:09:56,918 --> 00:09:59,411
我的骨盆底是我身体里最强壮的肌肉了
My pelvic floor is the strongest muscle in my body.

255
00:09:59,421 --> 00:10:01,046
- 是吗 - 我就是自己的手术钳
- Is it? - I am my own forceps.

256
00:10:07,395 --> 00:10:08,753
吉尔 这些是装饰胡桃
Oh Jill, those are decorative walnuts.

257
00:10:08,763 --> 00:10:12,023
真的吗 看起来太逼真了
Really? They look so real.

258
00:10:12,033 --> 00:10:13,124
是假的吗
They're fake?

259
00:10:13,134 --> 00:10:15,134
不 是真的胡桃
No, they're real.

260
00:10:19,107 --> 00:10:21,441
美味哟 看起来真棒
Yummy. You look good.

261
00:10:24,746 --> 00:10:26,679
我过去看看安迪
I'm gonna go check on Andy.

262
00:10:29,150 --> 00:10:30,508
我选对球道的
Like, I took the right line.

263
00:10:30,518 --> 00:10:32,877
打第十七洞时 我选对球道了
I took the right line on 17 it drops.

264
00:10:32,887 --> 00:10:34,879
我站在球岭错误的一边
I'm on the wrong half of the hourglass green.

265
00:10:34,889 --> 00:10:37,682
至少是个四十英尺的推杆 谁做到了
At any rate, it's a 40-foot putt. Who sinks it?

266
00:10:38,827 --> 00:10:40,827
我 我做到了 小菜一碟
This guy. I sunk it. Like it was nothing.

267
00:10:44,165 --> 00:10:45,623
大概只是胃灼热而已
Probably just heartburn.

268
00:10:45,633 --> 00:10:47,192
解酸剂能让你好受点
If you have antacid, that might help.

269
00:10:47,202 --> 00:10:48,893
谢谢 但是塔米认为大型制药厂
Oh thanks, but Tammy thinks Big Pharma

270
00:10:48,903 --> 00:10:51,529
是医疗产业最糟糕的部分
is the nadir of the medical-industrial complex.

271
00:10:51,539 --> 00:10:53,531
她当然这么觉得
Of course she does.

272
00:10:53,541 --> 00:10:54,966
如果她想啃的话
I have some shredded potato peels in the sink

273
00:10:54,976 --> 00:10:56,601
我的水槽里还有些土豆皮残渣
if she'd like to gnaw on those.

274
00:10:56,611 --> 00:10:57,802
这对胃灼热有帮助吗
Does that help heartburn?

275
00:10:57,812 --> 00:10:59,804
- 没有 - 那不用了
- No. - Of course not.

276
00:10:59,814 --> 00:11:02,707
我们家里有姜
We've got some ginger root at home.

277
00:11:02,717 --> 00:11:05,718
感谢你做的一切
Thanks for everything.

278
00:11:16,427 --> 00:11:19,057
五楼那个告诉我你是个医生
5C told me you're a doctor.

279
00:11:19,067 --> 00:11:21,626
我长了个脓疮 可能是水蛭咬的
I have an abscess and I think it might be leeching.

280
00:11:21,636 --> 00:11:24,529
你能看看吗
Can you take a look?

281
00:11:24,539 --> 00:11:25,838
进来吧
Come in.

282
00:11:29,544 --> 00:11:31,636
就像我们的祖先在最初的感恩节做的那样
As our ancestors did on the first Thanksgiving,

283
00:11:31,646 --> 00:11:33,513
让我们牵起手来
let us join hands.

284
00:11:37,085 --> 00:11:38,777
洛克哈特 你来唱祝词好吗
Lockhart, will you do the honors?

285
00:11:38,787 --> 00:11:39,919
当然
Of course.

286
00:11:43,483 --> 00:11:44,628
低下头
Bow your heads.

287
00:11:47,095 --> 00:11:49,649
感谢您赐给我们每日的食粮
We thank thee For this daily bread

288
00:11:52,471 --> 00:11:58,471
感谢您赐给我们美好的祝愿
For blessings on This table spread

289
00:11:58,650 --> 00:12:02,546
我们的主啊
Our Lord

290
00:12:02,000 --> 00:12:07,272
天堂上的主
In heaven

291
00:12:07,059 --> 00:12:12,059
阿门
Amen

292
00:12:14,214 --> 00:12:16,214
- 唱得很美 - 鸡皮疙瘩都起来了
- It was beautiful. - Goosebumps.

293
00:12:16,224 --> 00:12:18,016
- 谢谢 - 真迷人
- Thank you. - Gorgeous.

294
00:12:18,026 --> 00:12:20,118
现在 让我们来享受一场既美味
Now, let us enjoy a delicious

295
00:12:20,128 --> 00:12:23,688
又完美承袭了传统的感恩节晚餐
and historically accurate Thanksgiving feast.

296
00:12:23,698 --> 00:12:25,857
期待了一整天哟
Been looking forward to this all day.

297
00:12:25,867 --> 00:12:28,193
我辛勤劳动的果实
The harvest of my labors.

298
00:12:28,203 --> 00:12:29,331
啊
Ahh?!

299
00:12:29,941 --> 00:12:33,376
不好意思 有点惊喜罢了
I'm sorry, just surprised.

300
00:12:34,083 --> 00:12:36,067
烟熏鳗鱼
12 o'clock smoked eel,

301
00:12:36,077 --> 00:12:38,203
大西洋生牡蛎
2 o'clock raw Atlantic Oysters,

302
00:12:38,213 --> 00:12:41,706
温热的牛奶玉米粥
6:45 a lukewarm, milk and corn samp,

303
00:12:41,716 --> 00:12:43,741
还有龙虾驱干
9 o'clock lobster body.

304
00:12:43,751 --> 00:12:46,644
没有尾巴 没有爪子 也没有
There's no tails or claws or...

305
00:12:46,654 --> 00:12:50,315
开动吧各位
Enjoy everyone!

306
00:12:50,325 --> 00:12:52,750
- 哦 - 亲爱的 天啊
- Oh. - Oh honey, oh.

307
00:12:52,760 --> 00:12:54,719
- 我要死了 - 把食谱求过来
- I just died. - Get the recipe.

308
00:12:54,729 --> 00:12:56,988
玉米粥真是口味复杂
The samp has a complex mouth feel.

309
00:12:56,998 --> 00:12:59,357
她形容得让我觉得会有种呕吐物的口感
The way she described it, I thought it would taste like barf.

310
00:12:59,367 --> 00:13:02,293
好吧 你不吃的 我帮你吃完吧
Well, I finish whatever you don't have.

311
00:13:02,303 --> 00:13:03,795
我觉得我们能聚在一起过白色感恩节
I think it's wonderful we've been blessed

312
00:13:03,805 --> 00:13:05,196
真是太美好了
with a white Thanksgiving.

313
00:13:05,206 --> 00:13:07,298
史上最白
The whitest.

314
00:13:07,308 --> 00:13:09,000
吉尔 你感恩节的时候都做什么
Jill, what do you do on Thanksgiving?

315
00:13:09,010 --> 00:13:11,302
有什么犹太传统吗
Do you have any Jewish traditions?

316
00:13:11,312 --> 00:13:14,572
我是地道的美国人 所以 没有
Um, well I'm American so, no.

317
00:13:14,582 --> 00:13:17,008
我们一般都去我婆婆坎迪斯家
We usually we go to my mother-in-law, Candace's

318
00:13:17,018 --> 00:13:21,846
但她被困在了游船谋杀案的陪审团里
but she's sequestered on that Cruise Murder jury.

319
00:13:21,856 --> 00:13:23,314
真的吗 我超爱看那个庭审
Really? I love that trial.

320
00:13:23,324 --> 00:13:25,283
我也是 简直迷死了
Me too. I am obsessed.

321
00:13:25,293 --> 00:13:26,618
迷死了
I'm obsessed.

322
00:13:26,628 --> 00:13:28,052
肯定是他的妻子把他推下了船
The wife so pushed him overboard.

323
00:13:28,062 --> 00:13:29,995
- 没错 - 我是说 她就是凶手
- Yes! - I mean, she's totally guilty.

324
00:13:30,005 --> 00:13:31,055
完全没错
Totally!

325
00:13:31,065 --> 00:13:32,790
你知道他在出海前两周
Did you know that he filed for divorce

326
00:13:32,800 --> 00:13:34,726
提出了离婚吗
two weeks before the cruise?

327
00:13:34,736 --> 00:13:36,127
是的 布鲁克 我们都看了新闻报道了
Yes Brooke, we all watch Dateline.

328
00:13:36,137 --> 00:13:38,796
所有人都看了
Everyone, in the world.

329
00:13:38,806 --> 00:13:40,765
我们的确有个家庭传统
We do have one family tradition.

330
00:13:40,775 --> 00:13:41,866
我们一边绕着桌子
We go around the table

331
00:13:41,876 --> 00:13:43,601
一边说些感恩词
and say something we're thankful for.

332
00:13:43,611 --> 00:13:45,236
这个有意思 吉尔
Oh fun idea, Jill.

333
00:13:45,246 --> 00:13:46,771
我们来做点改进吧
I'd like to improve on it.

334
00:13:46,781 --> 00:13:48,706
让我们每个人都说一件
Let's each say one thing

335
00:13:48,716 --> 00:13:52,110
其它人应该抱有感激之情的事
someone else should be thankful for.

336
00:13:52,120 --> 00:13:55,914
让我第一个来
Okay, I'll go first. Hm.

337
00:13:55,924 --> 00:14:00,818
布鲁克 我认为你应该感激
Brooke, I think you should be thankful...

338
00:14:00,828 --> 00:14:04,088
莱克斯没有被起诉
Lex didn't get indicted.

339
00:14:04,098 --> 00:14:05,290
我们俩今年的幸运事
We have many blessings

340
00:14:05,300 --> 00:14:06,357
实在是太多了
to count this year.

341
00:14:06,367 --> 00:14:07,926
准确的说 是数不胜数
Millions, in fact!

342
00:14:07,936 --> 00:14:11,396
我认为肯定没有去年多
Not as many millions as last year,

343
00:14:11,406 --> 00:14:13,865
但是布鲁克 我最近看到一篇文章讲
but Brooke, I recently read an article saying that

344
00:14:13,875 --> 00:14:15,833
失去财富实际上是一种解脱
losing money can actually be a relief

345
00:14:15,843 --> 00:14:18,303
因为一旦你被身边的人远远的抛在身后
because once you fall so far behind the Joneses,

346
00:14:18,313 --> 00:14:21,005
你就摆脱了去追赶他们的压力
you're free from the pressure of having to keep up with them.

347
00:14:21,015 --> 00:14:23,683
没错 你看 的确值得感激 对不对 莱克斯
Yeah see? Something to be thankful for, right Lex?

348
00:14:28,022 --> 00:14:30,982
天啊 布鲁克是她们家最友善的一个
Oh my God. Brooke's the nice one.

349
00:14:30,992 --> 00:14:33,282
太被欺负了
She's Jan Brady!

350
00:14:39,374 --> 00:14:41,567
我们的祖先是第一批来到这里
Our ancestors were the first to colonize

351
00:14:41,577 --> 00:14:43,602
开拓疆土的人
the final frontier!

352
00:14:43,612 --> 00:14:45,905
在他们来到这片富饶的土地之前 这里一个人都没有
No one was here when they settled these rich lands.

353
00:14:45,915 --> 00:14:50,643
一个也没有 他们勇敢地登上船
No one! Aboard their ship,

354
00:14:50,653 --> 00:14:52,878
驶向一个新世界
they careened toward a New World.

355
00:14:52,888 --> 00:14:54,513
这些外来的勇士
Alien to its terrain,

356
00:14:54,523 --> 00:14:56,248
在陌生的异土
strangers to a strange land,

357
00:14:56,258 --> 00:14:59,159
他们改变了人类历史的进程
they changed the course of human history.

358
00:15:01,731 --> 00:15:05,199
他还没有说完 我认为他还没有说完
He's not done. I don't think he's done.

359
00:15:05,901 --> 00:15:07,626
没错
Yes they did!

360
00:15:07,636 --> 00:15:11,230
非常抱歉 突然打断了大家
I am sorry for the unexpected intermission everyone

361
00:15:11,240 --> 00:15:14,583
但是我终于找到了我下一个人生目标
but I finally figured out what I am going to do next.

362
00:15:14,593 --> 00:15:15,835
我打赌是开发一个应用程序
I bet it's an app.

363
00:15:15,845 --> 00:15:17,870
不 我保证是去竞选政府官员
No, running for office. Guaranteed.

364
00:15:17,880 --> 00:15:20,639
我要上火星
I'm going to Mars!

365
00:15:23,686 --> 00:15:24,877
我们错的好像有点远
We were way off.

366
00:15:24,887 --> 00:15:27,079
几光年吧
Light years.

367
00:15:27,089 --> 00:15:28,981
孩子们 让我们休息一下吧
Children, why don't you take five?

368
00:15:28,991 --> 00:15:31,250
莱克斯叔叔要开始他的表演了
Uncle Lex is gonna do a little show of his own

369
00:15:31,260 --> 00:15:33,152
你们待会再回来继续完成你们的节目
and then you can come back and finish.

370
00:15:33,162 --> 00:15:35,988
我不知道你们的节目和感恩节有没半毛钱关系 小朋友
I don't know what that play had to do with Thanksgiving, buddy

371
00:15:35,998 --> 00:15:39,633
但是我受益匪浅
but it really spoke to me.

372
00:15:39,969 --> 00:15:42,294
来吧 莱克斯 说说吧
So, Lex. I mean, do tell.

373
00:15:42,304 --> 00:15:45,664
你打算怎么降落在火星上
How did you land on Mars?

374
00:15:45,674 --> 00:15:48,334
我不会降落在火星上 巴洛特
I didn't land on Mars, Barrett.

375
00:15:48,344 --> 00:15:50,970
是火星降落在我身上
Mars landed on me.

376
00:15:50,980 --> 00:15:53,105
这是当下最受欢迎的游戏
It's the hottest game in town right now

377
00:15:53,115 --> 00:15:55,941
而且我想要一个前排座位
and I want a front row seat.

378
00:15:55,951 --> 00:15:57,818
我找到了我的使命
I found my calling in life.

379
00:15:59,189 --> 00:16:01,598
我是一名太空移民先驱
I am a Space Pilgrim.

380
00:16:01,608 --> 00:16:03,040
你怎么认为 布鲁克
What about you, Brooke?

381
00:16:03,050 --> 00:16:07,920
对于莱克斯想要上火星 你有什么看法
How do you feel about Lex going to Mars?

382
00:16:07,930 --> 00:16:10,089
当然 我认为这非常棒
Of course, I think it's great.

383
00:16:10,099 --> 00:16:12,925
我们冯·韦伯一家称霸地球后
After global domination the only place left

384
00:16:12,935 --> 00:16:15,761
唯一可以去的地方就是银河系了
for the Von Webers to go is intergalactic.

385
00:16:15,771 --> 00:16:17,838
对吧
Am I right?

386
00:16:19,775 --> 00:16:22,668
莱克斯 我支持你的梦想
Lex, I support you in your dream

387
00:16:22,678 --> 00:16:25,871
就像你支持我的一样
just as you supported me in mine.

388
00:16:25,881 --> 00:16:27,306
我爱你 宝贝儿
I love you, babe.

389
00:16:27,316 --> 00:16:29,341
我也爱你
Love you.

390
00:16:29,351 --> 00:16:33,212
太美好了 我真为你们感到开心呢
Aw cute! I'm so happy for you guys.

391
00:16:33,222 --> 00:16:37,116
但是我希望在太空 你们请不着秘书
But I hope they don't have secretaries in space.

392
00:16:37,126 --> 00:16:41,161
餐后甜点呢 我想知道清教徒会准备什么样的甜点
Dessert! What did the Pilgrims have for dessert?

393
00:16:41,597 --> 00:16:44,023
葡萄干 为什么巴洛特要这样糟蹋感恩节
Raisins?! Why does Barrett hate Thanksgiving?

394
00:16:44,033 --> 00:16:47,126
我也无从得知 亲爱的
I don't know, honey.

395
00:16:47,136 --> 00:16:49,128
我告诉你不要担心我
I told you not to worry about me.

396
00:16:49,138 --> 00:16:51,630
是 我现在当然不担心
Yep. Definitely not worried now.

397
00:16:51,640 --> 00:16:54,400
莱克斯 你确定你现在还好吗
Lex, are you sure you're feeling okay?

398
00:16:54,410 --> 00:16:56,802
前所未有的棒
I have never felt better.

399
00:16:56,812 --> 00:16:58,304
比连续三晚在红石剧场听
Not even when I was at night three

400
00:16:58,314 --> 00:17:00,714
费西乐队的感觉还要棒
of Phish at Red Rocks.

401
00:17:02,918 --> 00:17:04,176
这是一种过敏反应
It's an allergic reaction.

402
00:17:04,186 --> 00:17:05,644
但是我的肾病医生说
But my nephrologist said...

403
00:17:05,654 --> 00:17:07,680
等一下 吉尔
Hold on. Jill?

404
00:17:07,690 --> 00:17:10,049
奥莉的派对听起来真棒
Ollie's party sounds like so much fun.

405
00:17:10,059 --> 00:17:13,385
告诉我你吃了什么 慢慢说
Tell me everything you're eating and go slow.

406
00:17:13,395 --> 00:17:15,054
我并不在奥莉的派对上
Oh, I'm not at Ollie's.

407
00:17:15,064 --> 00:17:17,289
你听到的声音都是我的邻居 
That sound is the din of all of my neighbors

408
00:17:17,299 --> 00:17:18,924
在我的公寓里面喋喋不休
inside my apartment at once.

409
00:17:18,934 --> 00:17:20,126
等等 你在和你的邻居
Wait, you're doing Thanksgiving

410
00:17:20,136 --> 00:17:21,193
一起过感恩节
with your neighbors?

411
00:17:21,203 --> 00:17:22,928
没错 显然如此
Mm-hm. Apparently.

412
00:17:22,938 --> 00:17:25,331
我正要去给一个病人缝合瘘管 先别多问
Look, I gotta go suture a fistula. Don't ask.

413
00:17:25,341 --> 00:17:26,699
你什么时候回来
When are you back?

414
00:17:26,709 --> 00:17:27,800
这儿正在下雪 但是没什么
It's snowing here but nothing

415
00:17:27,810 --> 00:17:28,968
能阻止我今晚逃离
will prevent me from escaping

416
00:17:28,978 --> 00:17:31,904
这个地狱
this hell hole tonight.

417
00:17:31,914 --> 00:17:33,873
这是我过的最糟糕的感恩节
This is the worst Thanksgiving ever.

418
00:17:33,883 --> 00:17:35,174
我们可以明天一起做晚餐吗
Can we please do dinner tomorrow?

419
00:17:35,184 --> 00:17:37,743
火鸡 填料 肉汁
Turkey, stuffing, gravy.

420
00:17:37,753 --> 00:17:38,978
好多肉汁
So much gravy.

421
00:17:38,988 --> 00:17:41,247
同意 同意 我想给你一千个同意
Yes! Yes! A thousand times yes!

422
00:17:41,257 --> 00:17:42,281
你还好吗
Are you okay?

423
00:17:42,291 --> 00:17:43,716
你一般不会这么抓狂
You usually only go Pride & Prejudice

424
00:17:43,726 --> 00:17:44,783
除非情况糟糕到爆
when you're really losing it.

425
00:17:44,793 --> 00:17:46,352
你无法想象
Oh you have no idea.

426
00:17:46,362 --> 00:17:48,687
你怎么能让我来这种地方
How could you let me come here?

427
00:17:49,965 --> 00:17:52,166
我先挂了 明天见
I gotta go. See you tomorrow!

428
00:17:55,271 --> 00:17:58,831
四十一 四十二 我正在做凯格尔运动
41, 42. I'm doing my kegels.

429
00:17:58,841 --> 00:18:01,734
你可以坐在 好吧
Oh, you can sit... All right.

430
00:18:01,744 --> 00:18:05,004
一般来说 维持良好的姐妹关系并不轻松
Sisterhood isn't always easy, but

431
00:18:05,014 --> 00:18:08,707
但那只是一般情况 感恩节快乐
it is for always. Happy Thanksgiving.

432
00:18:08,717 --> 00:18:11,977
这两款包下个月才发售
These bags won't be in stores for a month

433
00:18:11,987 --> 00:18:14,446
我想让你们俩第一时间拿到 
and I want you guys to have the first ones.

434
00:18:14,456 --> 00:18:16,148
谢谢你 布鲁克
Thank you, Brooke.

435
00:18:16,158 --> 00:18:17,883
巴洛特 我想起来了
Barrett, this reminds me.

436
00:18:17,893 --> 00:18:19,885
你还没有给我看你那套托里·伯奇的裙子（美国时尚女装品牌）
You have not shown me your new Tory Burch.

437
00:18:19,895 --> 00:18:21,520
- 什么 - 你忘记了
- What?! - You haven't.

438
00:18:21,530 --> 00:18:24,023
好吧 你知道我有一个衣橱来放置我所有的衣服
Okay, you know that I have a closet with my entire collection.

439
00:18:24,033 --> 00:18:25,157
我把这件放在衣橱外面
I put this one on a pedestal.

440
00:18:25,167 --> 00:18:27,092
让它看上去更加优雅
It is breath-taking.

441
00:18:27,102 --> 00:18:30,429
好吧 我是一家快速发展的 
Okay, I am the founder and She-E-O

442
00:18:30,439 --> 00:18:32,698
零售品牌的创始人和总裁
of one of the fastest growing retail brands

443
00:18:32,708 --> 00:18:34,867
救命呀
- in the country! - Cul de Sac.

444
00:18:34,877 --> 00:18:36,702
你一向自我感觉这么棒吗
Well aren't you impressed with yourself?

445
00:18:36,712 --> 00:18:38,837
我是说 又不是路易 威登
I mean, it's not like you're Louis Vuitton,

446
00:18:38,847 --> 00:18:42,141
被大规模地山寨 卖到大街小巷去
getting knocked off and sold on every street corner.

447
00:18:42,151 --> 00:18:44,810
远远还赶不上
I mean, hardly.

448
00:18:44,820 --> 00:18:46,946
几乎所有的野餐烧烤和街区聚会
Every BBQ or block party there's a version of

449
00:18:46,956 --> 00:18:48,347
都能看到巴洛特的土豆沙拉
Barrett's potato salad.

450
00:18:48,357 --> 00:18:50,149
每个人都想要自己做一份
Everyone tries to recreate it,

451
00:18:50,159 --> 00:18:52,051
但是都和原创相差甚远
nothing competes with the original.

452
00:18:52,061 --> 00:18:54,153
秘诀就是我自制的沙拉酱
The secret is I make my own mayonnaise.

453
00:18:54,163 --> 00:18:56,822
巴洛特自己做的沙拉酱
Barrett makes her own mayonnaise.

454
00:18:56,832 --> 00:18:59,158
天啊 什么都是巴洛特  
Ugh! Barrett! Barrett! Barrett!

455
00:19:06,508 --> 00:19:08,867
噢 这个袋子太棒了
Ah, this... is stunning!

456
00:19:08,877 --> 00:19:09,902
没错
Oh it is.

457
00:19:09,912 --> 00:19:11,303
这绝对是一个完美的浴室脚垫
Oh my gosh, I could do a really great bath mat.

458
00:19:11,313 --> 00:19:13,765
或者当作一个枕头 把里面塞满然后把前面缝起来
Or a pillow. Put it in and then close the top.

459
00:19:13,775 --> 00:19:15,116
没错
Yes.

460
00:19:19,754 --> 00:19:22,585
布鲁克 你还好 蛋糕
Brooke? Are you o... cake!

461
00:19:28,306 --> 00:19:31,072
太好吃了 太好吃了
So good. So good.

462
00:19:32,374 --> 00:19:33,891
布鲁克 我懂你的心情
Brooke, I know it's hard.

463
00:19:33,901 --> 00:19:36,060
别看着我
Oh, don't look at me.

464
00:19:36,070 --> 00:19:37,528
别让她们影响你
Don't let them get to you.

465
00:19:37,538 --> 00:19:39,396
她们不过是两个肤浅的满怀妒忌的家伙
They're blonde, jealous turds.

466
00:19:39,406 --> 00:19:43,868
吃不到葡萄才会说葡萄酸
They hate ya' because they ain't ya!

467
00:19:43,878 --> 00:19:46,136
巴洛特可以把蛋糕寄些给我吗
Do you think Barrett ships her cakes?

468
00:19:46,146 --> 00:19:47,605
她们不是嫉妒
They're not jealous.

469
00:19:47,615 --> 00:19:50,341
她们是在向我炫耀她们的幸福生活
They love flaunting their perfect lives.

470
00:19:50,351 --> 00:19:52,142
她们的孩子不是捣蛋鬼
Their kids aren't hell cats.

471
00:19:52,152 --> 00:19:55,379
她们的奖牌不是参与奖
Their Olympic medals aren't for participation.

472
00:19:55,389 --> 00:19:58,249
你的几个孩子就是天使的礼物
Your kids are pooped from angels.

473
00:19:58,259 --> 00:20:00,484
霍桑可能并没有外遇
And Hawthorne might not cheat,

474
00:20:00,494 --> 00:20:02,253
但是洛克哈特肯定 
but Lockhart definitely knows

475
00:20:02,263 --> 00:20:04,329
在外面乱搞过
what a dick tastes like.

476
00:20:05,035 --> 00:20:06,535
这是一种直觉
It's a gut instinct.

477
00:20:08,470 --> 00:20:11,161
虽然你们这帮犹太人都是移民过来的
Even though your people came through Ellis Island,

478
00:20:11,171 --> 00:20:14,064
但你比她们都更像我的家人
you're more my family than they are.

479
00:20:14,074 --> 00:20:17,043
布鲁克 家人
Brooke, family...

480
00:20:17,489 --> 00:20:20,735
- 吉尔 你还好吗 - 天啊
- Jill, are you... - Yes!

481
00:20:20,745 --> 00:20:25,284
那是宝宝性别揭秘派对的蛋糕 我的天啊
That's the cake for my gender reveal party! Oh my God!

482
00:20:36,719 --> 00:20:38,711
是个女孩
It's a girl!

483
00:20:42,347 --> 00:20:44,505
不
No!

484
00:20:45,439 --> 00:20:48,247
我 的 天
Oh... my... God!

485
00:20:49,017 --> 00:20:52,348
为什么
Why?

486
00:20:53,136 --> 00:20:54,816
为什么
Why?

487
00:20:57,983 --> 00:21:00,144
关于乡下我说错了
I was wrong about the suburbs.

488
00:21:00,154 --> 00:21:01,645
那不是个充满恐怖气息的房子
It's not a house of horrors,

489
00:21:01,655 --> 00:21:04,448
而是个充满鼾声的房子
it's a house of snores.

490
00:21:06,627 --> 00:21:09,320
那里没有人性的黑暗
There's no darkness.

491
00:21:09,330 --> 00:21:11,663
没有秘密
No secrets.

492
00:21:15,102 --> 00:21:16,702
只有平庸无聊
Just banality.

493
00:21:21,542 --> 00:21:24,435
你保证我们再也不会去那儿了好吗
Promise we never have to go back there again?

494
00:21:24,445 --> 00:21:26,364
我保证
I promise.

